MohammadReza Shahbazi

Front-end Developer

CONTACT

Phone

+98-9391886467

Email

shahbaziweb@gmail.com

Home

Iran - Tehran

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

SASS

Angular 2+

Typescript

Restful API

Javascript

Nativescript

JQuery

C#

FOLLOW ME

Telegram

itismohammadreza

LinkedIn

mohammadrezashahbazi



ABOUT ME

Born in 1995. Graduated in computer engineering - software orientation. Interested in new and tough challenges, strongly agrees and interested in teamwork. Provability in optimizing web functionalities that improve data retrieval workflow efficiencies. Proficient in creating user interface, troubleshooting simple/complex issues and features based on user feedback.

Experienced working with teams of 30+ people.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Q	Front-end Developer	2017 - 2017
П	Rayak Negar Pars Company	

TAM Company

Lead Front-end Developer 2020 - 2021

Agah e-Commerce Company

Front-end Developer 2021 - Now

Rubika



EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Engineering

Azad University, South Tehran Branch

2014 - 2018



COURSES & CERTIFICATES

Certified Internet Web Professional (CIW)

Tehran Institute of Technology (2016)

Jquery & Bootstrap

Tehran Institute of Technology (2016)